365chess.com 2019-03-11

# Privacy Policy - 365Chess.com

Safeguarding the information provided to 365Chess.com is our main concern.

This policy explains how 365Chess.com treat, uses, and if necessary, discloses your personal information. It is important that you know and fully understand our Privacy Policy before using our website.

## Collection of information

As part of our services, tools and processes we ask for your name, address and other contact information like demographic information. While some of the information you provide is essential to run our site, other information is optional, clearly marked as such, and may be given at your discretion. 

365Chess.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, 365Chess.com cookie information, and the page you request. 

The information you provide allows us to provide an efficient service to you and helps us improve our level of service to better meet your needs.

## Cookies

To enhance your experience while visiting 365Chess.com, many of our web pages use "cookies". A "cookie" is a small piece of data stored on the user's computer that identifies you as a unique user. This piece of data contains information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personal information while using our site; they allow your navigation through our site to be more enjoyable.

## Your Personal Information

You can edit your 365Chess.com personal information at any time you want. 

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to our site or services, such as announcements, administrative messages, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. 

You will also receive the 365Chess.com Newsletter. At any time you shall be able to request the company to stop sending this information.

## Security

365Chess.com undertakes not to sell or let the aforesaid information to third parties nor use or process it for any purposes other than those described in this document. At any time, you shall be able to enforce the rights acknowledged by these provisions to request the data kept within the site member's area be modified or cancelled. The foregoing shall be valid except as otherwise required by law or court order.
